we've held six different solution
reasons on 6 different topics and we
came up with an amazing solution for
each and every one of them that we could
implement now if we had 10,000 people
and $100,000
we started with education and after an
hour we had an idea that we could
catalog existing information that's
already out there cross-referenced for
your interest in your learning style so
you could easily find a way to teach
your kid math based on their interests
for food we talked about creating an app
that helps us either Garden and
coordinate with neighbors know what when
it needs to be watered know where to
plant things know how much yield you got
and or a recipe by an app that you will
help you do the intellectual work of
figuring out what's for dinner and what
that entails and possibly coordinating
with your neighbors to bring down the
cost of the goods as well as the the
labor involved we talked about
infectious disease and how our lack of
trust in our governments in the media is
costing us dearly and so having a way to
share in to share our personal data of
what we're doing and what what we if we
get cope in nineteen how that impacts us
and how we recover and we know to find
solutions together in a way that our
data is safe it'll only happen in my
opinion if we have a cooperatively owned
tech company that we can trust and that
is transparent that isn't leaving this
up to Google or governments as well as
having a sense making platform a place
we can go to for accurate information
form to 10,000 of us right we don't need
to make it for the entire world but
making something that we trust for cope
at 19 or whatever another infectious
disease is coming down the line we
talked about community and we came up
with this idea of having a hundred
groups of 100 each group of 100 working
on a different meta problem for a
physical Dunbar group so one group
tackles plumbing and other group tackles
food sovereignty not their group tackles
child care and at the end you have
physical communities that are created
geographically but
but you as an individual part of the ten
thousand are connected to every other
group of 100 based on the fact you're
solving a problem together with them and
each of your hundred are probably in a
different community we talked about
transportation and we came up with both
a ride-sharing app that we all own
together and all of the beauty that's
entailed with that how they can
problem-solving and create creative
solutions together and also this idea of
a transportation hub in an in a major
city with 10,000 people participating
where every day there is a pickup and a
drop-off to every residents so that you
can get your goods from one person that
sent you to the other whether you have a
business or you're just selling
something on Craigslist you can actually
easily get the the good transported
between the two then our last solution
raising was on labor and we talked about
having a volunteer platform that helped
you find where your skills and desire
could could match or you could find out
where you can best contribute from who
you are and very easily tied to that was
just basically the same thing but with
money involved how do you get paid to do
those things how do we coordinate your
schedule so you're having almost all of
your labor being paid for is that I mean
to market yourself and you defined
client it's a knee into do to all that
so in six hour long conversations we
came up with six different solutions
that are powerful and definitely
possible with 10,000 people and $100,000
and so that is what we are doing next is
we're gonna hold a solution raising on
solution raising and find co-create how
could we get 10,000 people on $100,000
then how do we work through this process
to actually pick one of them and improve
it together and go through the process
of creating it together with 10,000
people which we don't have yet
and $100,000 and so I will put the
Facebook group solution raising in the
description please come join be part of
the solution raising be part of creating
solutions together because the world
needs solutions now more than ever
please like and subscribe share with
someone who you think could use this
message right now solutions are coming
down the pipe we're gonna create them
together and we can already see humanity
coming together on Koba 19 we're not
leaving it up to our elected officials
we're not leaving it up to the media
we're collecting information we're
crowdsourcing solutions and we're here
to help those on the front line and I'm
choosing to concentrate on that part and
concentrate on what I can do because I
have very little to offer in the COPE at
19 crisis itself everything is six
months to a year down the line but what
if we had known a year ago that this was
gonna happen what would we have in place
to be able to make this not just an okay
time but a time to thrive for Humanity
what can we create out of this so please
like and subscribe and hit the little
battle and we are gonna create so many
solutions together thank you